

# SAKSHI PRASAD





🕋 778-668-2604 💟 sakshiprasad26@gmail.com 🧕 Vancouver, Canada 👜 www.sakshidesigns.ca







www.linkedin.com/in/sakshi-prasad26

### PROJECTS

### GAME PREVIEW APPLICATION | August 2022 - Present

- · This is an academic project ongoing for the Google certificate course.
- · Solved customers' problems of booking and previewing games in advance by designing a user-friendly application to check out the arcade in the comfort of home.
- Creating a virtual experience where they can book game slots in advance.
- High-Fidelity design completed.

### MAUI APPLICATION | September 2022 - Present

- Working in a team of three as an intern.
- · Built a .net application for clients to decrease the difficulty in printing labels for the devices and make the work faster and more efficient.
- Phase 1 was to design and implement the homepage where data is fetched from Datto.
- Phase 2 is to design and implement the selected item view and then connect the page to the printer.

### WEBINAR FOR INTERNATIONAL STUDENTS | May 2021 - August 2021

- Proposed scope, project charter, and business case to coordinate a webinar.
- · Analyzed risks involved and devised a management plan to reduce the risk occurrences and establish a plan to resolve the issues.
- Prepared business reports and presentations.
- Used Project Libre and Monday to monitor the progress of the project.

### CONNECT DOCTORS APPLICATION | January 2021 - April 2021

- · Coordinated a team of five members.
- Formulized a platform for doctors who can advise with one click and patients to easily find and contact the
- Designed the user interface of the android application from scratch.
- Coded the admin section of the application in Java and XML.

### WORK EXPERIENCE

### **UI DESIGN INTERN**

TBITS IT Specialists, Vancouver | April 2022 - Present

- Designing the layout for users of an android application.
- · Ideation of the process and creating a portfolio.
- Creating an android application to solve the label printing problem for the clients.

### TECH SPECIALIST

### The/La Source. Burnaby | July 2022 - Present

- · Design planograms and cross-sell products and services.
- Collaborated with supervisors to escalate and address customer inquiries or technical issues.
- Documented support interactions for future reference.
- Solved a diverse range of technical issues across multiple systems and applications for customers and end-users across various time zones.
- Explained technical information in clear terms to promote better understanding for non-technical users.

Pearson Professional Centre, Vancouver | Sept 2020 - Sept 2021

- · Invigilated candidates while testing and made sure everyone complies with testing procedures.
- Implemented program-level departmental policies and procedures.
- Scheduled educational activities and departmental events to drive the mission and values of the institution.
- · Maintained program files, records, databases, and websites to gather research and prepare and submit daily reports.

### ADMINSTRATIVE ASSISTANT

Elite Immigration, New Westminster | Nov 2019 - July 2020

- Processed legal forms on the immigration portal and proofread all documents in the database.
- · Answered multi-line phone system, routed calls, delivered messages to staff, and greeted visitors.
- · Generated reports and typed letters in Word and prepared PowerPoint presentations.
- Maintained company handbook to outline policies and provide insights into company mission and values.

## Profile

A meticulous candidate with solid capabilities in designing, frontend, business dynamics, and solution generation. Self-motivated and positioned to contribute strongly through skills and enthusiasm and an exemplary work ethic. Worked for three years with various Canadian companies in diverse fields.

### CERTIFICATES

- Google UX Design Level 4 (Pursuing)
- · Building Wireframes and Low -Fidelity Prototypes
- · Foundations of User Experience Design
- · Start the UX Design Process: Empathize, Define and Ideate

### EDUCATION

### PDD PROJECT MANAGEMENT

Douglas College, New Westminster, Canada 2021 - 2022

### PDD INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

Douglas College, New Westminster, Canada 2019 - 2021

### **BACHELOR OF TECHNOLOGY**

Rajasthan Technical University, Jaipur, India 2014 - 2018

### SKILLS

- User Experience Design using Figma, Adobe xD and Sketch.
- · Graphic Designing using Adobe Illustrator and Photoshop.
- Project Management using Project Libre and
- Client Communications and support.

### PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

- · C# and XAML using Visual Studio Community
- · Java and XML using Android Studio
- HTML AND CSS using Visual Studio Code

### INTERESTS

- Roller skating and Dancing
- Drawing caricatures
- · Storytelling through videos around the city

### IMMIGRATION STATUS

CANADA: Post Graduation Work Permit issued in July 2022